(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T01:29:21.748000",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
EXPO会場でも展示中の商品をご紹介。
Introducing products currently on display at the EXPO venue.
ホロライブ アクリルスタンド Bright Parade！
Hololive Acrylic Stand Bright Parade!
どんじゃらや一番くじなど
Donjara, Ichiban Kuji, and more,
たくさんの商品が発売いたします。
a wide variety of products will be released.
ホロライブ ルームキー風アクリルチャーム
Hololive Room Key Acrylic Charm
「ロボ子さん」がRelax timeで登場予定！
'Roboco-san' is coming in Relax time!
一番くじ ホロライブ アートアクリルコレクション
Ichiban Kuji Hololive Art Acrylic Collection
会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
Venue-limited goods are also being given away for free!
プレバンではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえるチャンス！
Chance to get immediate-use coupons on Premium Bandai!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiß Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも青春しよう！
Let's have our youth on the Weiß Schwarz stage too!
プレミアムブースター ホロライブプロダクション サマーコレクション
Premium Booster Hololive Production Summer Collection
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロスターズがヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
HOLOSTARS makes its debut in Weiß Schwarz Blau!
ようこそカードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the stage of card games!
スタートデッキ＆ブースターパック ホロスターズ
Start Deck & Booster Pack HOLOSTARS
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが新衣装になって再登場！
Hololive members' Nendoroids return with brand-new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリューから「ホロライブ」プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に
FuRyu's 'Hololive' prizes are coming to amusement facilities nationwide!
続々登場！
Appearing one after another!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
All domestic Hololive members are scheduled to be featured in the future!
最新情報はキャラ広場 ホロライブで検索！
Search Chara-Hiroba Hololive for the latest info!
フリュー
FuRyu
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Because fragments of you live in this heart,
一人じゃないから
Because I am not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Within the words I sketched one day,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
The scenery beyond closed eyes wavered.
少し戸惑う風の中 響く
Amidst the hesitant wind resounding,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping flower petals, our voices.
一瞬 一瞬
A fleeting moment,
捕まえるみたいに
As if trying to catch it,
もっと もっと 踏み出してみたら
If we take another step further...
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Because fragments of you live in this heart,
強くなくてもいい
It's okay even if you aren't strong,
今の光を
This present light,
僕と 集め 空に放つ
Gathering it together to release to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせから
We will gently let this miracle shine,
力が湧くから
Because power wells up within us.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clasping new seeds tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
We sowed them toward a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては
Making the wind of hope blow,
理想の花びら 祈る 明日の空
Petals of ideals, praying to tomorrow's sky.
何百 億も
Hundreds, billions of them,
光る星みたいに
Like shining stars,
ずっと ずっと 終わらないから
They will never, ever end.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて
This smile embraces the past,
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
Extending this hand toward the future.
時に転いでも
Even if times turn around,
空を見上げよう
Let's look up at the sky.
笑い泣いた日々を 刻んでゆく
Carving out the days we laughed and cried.
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから
Promising to seize our next dream,
踏み出そう ここから
Let's step forward from here.
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to hold that dream in my hands.
触れた奇跡の中で
Within the miracle we touched.
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
If we blend into the sky extending beyond,
君の場所と今をつなげたくて
Wanting to connect your place with the present.
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから
Because fragments of you live in this heart,
強くなくてもいい
It's okay even if you aren't strong,
今の光を
This present light,
僕と 集め 空に放つ
Gathering it together to release to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせから
We will gently let this miracle shine,
咲かせよう ここから
Let's make it bloom from right here.
一人じゃないから
Because I am not alone.
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
hololive stage2
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: For Visitors
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment オフィシャルグッズ
hololive 5th fes. Official Merchandise
ホロライブプロダクション ウエハース
Hololive Production Wafers
など、たくさんの商品が発売いたします！
And many more products will be released!
バンダイ／BANDAI SPIRITSブースでは会場限定グッズも無料配布中！
Free venue-exclusive goods are also being distributed at the Bandai / BANDAI SPIRITS booth!
プレミアムバンダイではすぐに使えるクーポンももらえる！
You can also get coupons you can use right away on Premium Bandai!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
楽しむ準備はいい？
Are you ready to have fun?
ヴァイスシュヴァルツの舞台でも、青春しよう！
Let's have our youth on the Weiss Schwarz stage too!
プレミアムブースター…
Premium Booster...
ホロライブプロダクション Summer Collection
Hololive Production Summer Collection
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロスターズが
Holostars...
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウに登場！
appears in Weiss Schwarz Blau!
ようこそ、カードゲームの舞台へ！
Welcome to the card game stage!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツブラウ スタートデッキ＆ブースターパック ホロスターズ 好評発売中！
Weiss Schwarz Blau Start Deck & Booster Pack Holostars Now on Sale!
ブシロード！
Bushiroad!
ホロライブメンバーのねんどろいどが新衣装になって再登場！
Hololive members' Nendoroids return in new outfits!
新しいねんどろいどをお楽しみに！
Look forward to the new Nendoroids!
フリューから『ホロライブ』プライズが全国アミューズメント施設に
Hololive prizes from Furyu are coming to amusement facilities nationwide
2024年7月以降に続々登場！
appearing one after another starting July 2024!
今後国内のホロライブメンバー全員展開予定！
All domestic Hololive members are scheduled to be featured!
フリュー
Furyu
推しの曲、めっちゃいいよね！
Your oshi's song is so good!
みるハコちゃーん！
Miruhako!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる！
With Miruhako, you can fully enjoy your oshi's content with a sense of presence!
みるハコ最高！推し活増やそう、みるハコ！
Miruhako is the best! Let's increase our oshi activities with Miruhako!
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから 一人じゃないから
because a piece of you is in this heart, because I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Inside the words we drew someday,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
the colorful scenery flickered beyond closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中 響く
Resounding in the slightly bewildered wind,
重なる花びら 私たちの声
overlapping petals are our voices.
一瞬一瞬捕らえるみたいに
Like capturing every single moment,
もっともっともっと踏み出せたら 【we are one】
if we could step forward more and more... [We are one]
あの涙が今の僕らを繋げて (繋げて)
Those tears connect us right now (connect us),
この心に君のカケラがあるから
because a piece of you is in this heart.
強くなくてもいい 今の光を
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather
僕と (君と) 集め (すべて) 空に放つ
the current light together (with you) and release it into the sky (all of it).
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから (その手で) 力が湧くから
We'll softly make this miracle shine together (with those hands), because it gives us strength.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clasping a new seed tightly,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
I sowed it with strong wishes toward the distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては (泳ぐ)
Letting the wind of hope blow (swimming),
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
ideal petals pray for tomorrow's sky.
何百億も光る星みたいに
Like hundreds of millions of shining stars,
ずっとずっとずっと終わらないから
it will never, ever end.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて (抱きしめて)
This smile warmly embraces the past (embraces it),
今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
and now I'll reach out my hand toward the future.
時に転んでも (それでいい) 空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes (that's fine), let's look up at the sky.
笑い (泣いた) 日々を (すべて) 刻んでゆく
Carving out the days we laughed (and cried) [all of them].
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから (その手で) 踏み出そう ここから
I promise we'll seize our next dream (with those hands), so let's step forward from here.
(we are with you) (we are with you) 同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手ニしたい
(We are with you) (We are with you) I want to see the same future, I want to make that dream mine.
(we are with you, capture the moment) 触れた奇跡の中で
(We are with you, capture the moment) Within the miracle we touched,
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
if we blend into the sky extending beyond...
hololive stage2 / #hololivefes EXPO24_DAY1
[hololive stage 2 / #hololivefes EXPO24_DAY1]
まもなく開演いたします
[The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: For Visitors]
hololive SUPER EXPO 2024 & hololive 5th fes. オフィシャルグッズ販売期間
[hololive SUPER EXPO 2024 & 5th fes. Official Merchandise Sales Period]
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで
Those tears connect us right now,
この心に君のカケラがいるから一人じゃないから
Because a piece of you is in my heart, I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中
Inside the words I once envisioned,
目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
The scenery coloring behind closed eyes wavered.
少し戸惑う風の中 (響く)
In the slightly hesitant wind (echoing),
重なる花びら 私たちの声
Overlapping flower petals, our voices.
一瞬 一瞬 捕らえるみたいに
As if capturing every single moment,
もっと もっと 踏み出せたら
If we could take another step forward
【we are one】
[We are one]
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで (繋いで)
Those tears connect us right now (connect us),
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because a piece of you is in my heart,
強くなくてもいい (なくてもいい)
It's okay not to be strong (it's okay),
今の光を 僕と (君と) 集め (すべて) 空に放つ
Gathering today's light with you, releasing it to the sky,
この奇跡を僕らでそっと 輝かせるから 力が湧くから
We'll make this miracle shine gently as strength wells up.
新たな種を握りしめ
Clutching new seeds in our hands,
遠い未来へと強く願い込め撒いた
We scattered them with strong wishes toward a distant future.
希望の風を吹かせては (泳ぐ)
Letting the winds of hope blow (swimming through),
理想の花びら 祈る明日の空
Ideal flower petals praying to tomorrow's sky.
何百億も光る星みたいに ずっと 終わらないから
Like hundreds of billions of shining stars, it will never end.
この笑顔が過去を強く抱きしめて 今未来にこの手伸ばしてゆくから
This smile firmly embraces the past as I reach out to the future.
時 転んでも (それでいい) 空を見上げよう
Even if we stumble sometimes (that's fine), let's look up.
笑い (泣いた) 日々を (すべて) 刻んでゆく
Carving out the days we laughed and cried (all of them),
次の夢を掴み取るって約束するから 踏み出そう ここから
Promising to seize our next dream, let's step forward.
【we are with you we are with you】
[We are with you, we are with you]
同じ未来を見 ていたい あの夢 手にしたい
Wanting to see the same future, wanting that dream.
【we are with you capture the moment】 触れた奇跡の中で
[We are with you, capture the moment] Amidst the miracle,
その先まで続く空にまぎれたら
If we get lost in the endless sky beyond,
君の場所と今をつなぎたくて
I want to connect your place with the present.
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで (繋いで)
Those tears connect us right now (connect us),
この心に君のカケラがいるから
Because a piece of you is in my heart.
強くなくてもいい (なくてもいい)
It's okay not to be strong (it's okay),
今の光を 僕と (君と) 集め (すべて) 空に放つ
Gathering today's light with you, releasing it to the sky,
この奇跡を僕らでそっと 輝かせるから 咲かせよう ここから (一緒に)
We'll make this miracle shine, let's bloom from here together.
一人じゃないから 【we are one】
Because we're not alone [We are one].
あの涙が今の僕らを繋いで
Those tears connect us now,
夢の色が変わっても 変わらないメロディ
Even if the color of our dreams changes, this unchanging melody
君のために 僕らのために
Is for you, is for us—
歌おう
Let's sing out!
いつまでも輝き続ける僕らの奇跡は 終わらないよ
Our sparkling miracle will never end, shining on forever!
涙さえ きっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn even our tears into a new start,
信じてくれる仲間と 一緒に 遠くへと
Together with the friends who believe in us, far away,
どこへだって飛び出して行こう もっと遠く
Let's leap out anywhere, even further beyond!
空を越えて
Crossing the skies—
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, to you whom we have yet to meet,
伝えたいこと たくさん あるんだ
There are so many things we want to tell you.
伝えたい今は 当たり前なんかじゃない
The present we want to share is nothing to take for granted—
翼を広げた
We spread our wings,
高鳴る鼓動
With our hearts beating fast!
手のひら つないでいくよ
Joining our hands together,
光の中 夢の先へ
Into the light, beyond our dreams,
羽ばたく雪は 君の願い
The fluttering snow is your wish.
みんなで掴んだ この奇跡が
This miracle we all grasped together
途切れないように 歌うんだ
We'll sing so it never fades away.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Higher and higher, with a loud voice!
僕らの未来を届け どこまでも
Delivering our future to wherever it may reach,
響かせていくよ ひとりじゃないメロディ
Resounding our melody, because we're not alone.
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 道に迷った 時がチャンスだ
Run slowly, run on! When you lose your way, that's your chance.
今日はみつけてくれてありがとう
Thank you for finding me today!
目の前のことに がむしゃらで 間違いは数えきれなくて
So reckless with what's right in front of us, mistakes too countless to count,
一つのことに 手いっぱいで
Putting our all into just one thing,
ただ前しか見えてなくて まだすぐ進むの?
Only able to look straight ahead—are we moving forward already?
キラキラした言葉をもつ 必ず行こう
Holding sparkling words, let's surely go on.
圧力に押されそう 忘れたくないよ
Almost crushed by the pressure, but I don't want to forget.
ただ好きの気持ち ずっとの興味ばかりを
Just holding onto that simple feeling of love and endless curiosity,
気にするのはやめよう ゆっくり走れ 走れ
Let's stop worrying about it! Run slowly, run on,
道に迷った 時がチャンスだ 何にもないない
When you lose your way, that's your chance—when you have nothing at all,
新しい僕が見つかるはずさ できっこないことばかり見えて
You'll find a new self! Seeing only things that can't be done,
クルクルいつも遠回り だけど昨日よりは
Spinning around in detours as always, but compared to yesterday,
道が見えるんならもう大丈夫
If you can see the path ahead, then everything's alright!
踏み出してしまった 道は なかなか戻りづらくなって
The path we stepped onto has grown hard to turn back from,
これも一つの経験だ たった一人の人生だ
But this too is an experience, this is just one person's life.
分からないことは 分からないと 言い出せない
We can't bring ourselves to admit when we don't understand something,
臆病な僕の みんなは攻めなかった
In our cowardice, no one blamed us.
忘れたくないよ この僕の気持ち
I don't want to forget this feeling of mine,
誰かを演じてた 嘘はもうやめよう
Let's stop pretending to be someone else with lies.
ゆっくり走れ 走れ 風が吹いたら進め 正面だ
Run slowly, run on! When the wind blows, move straight ahead,
何にもないない それよりも先は 僕次第だから
When there's nothing at all, what lies beyond depends on me!
できっこないことばかり見えて クルクルいつも遠回り
Seeing only things that can't be done, spinning around in detours,
だけど昨日よりは 道が見えるんならもう大丈夫
But if you can see the path ahead better than yesterday, then it's alright!
今年で結成の目玉一となります
This year marks our milestone anniversary!
あの一等星のさんざめく光で
With the dazzling light of that first-magnitude star,
あなたとダンスを踊ろうか
Shall I dance with you?
我が太陽系の鼓動に合わせて
Matching the heartbeat of our solar system,
絡まったステップで煌めいて、星っ！
Sparkle with entangled steps, star!
ランバダ ルンバ ふたり 宇宙でランデブーな
Rambada, Rumba, the two of us having a rendezvous in space,
妄、惑って 夜夜眠れない
Delirious with delusion, unable to sleep night after night.
星座になって 混ざる どんな一等星も
Becoming a constellation and mingling—no first-magnitude star
あなたに代わる 光度はないわ
Has a luminosity that can replace you.
校舎の裏あの日あなた見つけた
Behind the school building, that day, I found you,
奇跡さえ 今も はなれない
Even that miracle still hasn't left me.
隣に 繁く 見える 冥王星も
Even Pluto, visible nearby so frequently,
生憎、今は興味がないわ
Unfortunately, I have no interest in it right now.
星が舞いちゃって
Stars are dancing,
胸が鳴っちゃって
My heart is beating,
気付けば彼方――
Before I knew it, far away—
あの一等星のさんざめく光で
With the dazzling light of that first-magnitude star,
あなたとダンスを踊ろうか
Shall I dance with you?
我が太陽系の法則に誘われ
Seduced by the laws of our solar system,
交わった感度で煌めいて、星っ！
Sparkle with intersecting sensitivity, star!
オー・オ・オー！
Oh-oh-oh!
星間線を繋いで
Connecting the interstellar lines,
あなたに届け
Reaching out to you,
宇宙の果てから
From the edge of the universe,
あなた 侵光系！
You are a phototactic system!
ランバダ ルンバ ふたり 宇宙でランデブーな
Rambada, Rumba, the two of us having a rendezvous in space,
妄、惑って 夜夜眠れない
Delirious with delusion, unable to sleep night after night.
星座になって 混ざる どんな一等星も
Becoming a constellation and mingling—no first-magnitude star
あなたに代わる 光度はないわ
Has a luminosity that can replace you.
ラララ...
La la la...
女神 聖女 聡明 慈愛 博愛 デスわ！
Goddess, saint, wisdom, love, charity—that's right!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ?
Lights on me, all shining, complete with a prince?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね(イェイ)
What kinda dream for a plain girl like me to be a princess—just kidding! (Yay)
バイト探し 採用ないし
Unemployed, searching for a job with no success,
やけになって飛び込む
Desperate, I dive into
場違いすぎる世界
A world where I don't belong at all.
パシリばかり 雑用係
Running errands, doing all the chores,
最悪の奴らのマネージャー就任です
Appointed as manager to these awful guys.
バレたら最後
If I'm found out, it's the end—
貶められるの嫌だし 生きてるためだし
I hate being humiliated, but I'm just trying to survive.
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ?
Pampered by a prince and everything?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね
What a dream for a plain girl like me to become a princess.
私をプロデュースして
Produce me,
髪も服も全部可愛くして
Make my hair and clothes entirely cute.
いつか出会う王子様どこで何をしているの?神様
Where and what are you doing, future prince? Oh God,
待っていますから気長に(はぁ...)
I'll be waiting patiently! (Haa...)
ある日出会う 運命のひと
Then one day, I meet my destined someone,
紳士な振る舞いにドキドキしちゃったんだ
His gentlemanly demeanor made my heart race.
名前なんて聞けるはずはない
There's no way I could ask his name,
また会いたいなんて願っているだけでした
I could only wish to see him once more.
時間が止まる「また会えたね」と君
Time stops as you say, "We met again."
やっぱり恋だ
It's definitely love.
きっと少女漫画じゃ両想い
Surely in a shoujo manga, it's mutual,
ベタでいいじゃんむしろベタがいいじゃん
Clichés are great, actually cliches are best!
モブ女の私もヒロインなる気ありますなんてね
Even a background girl like me wants to be the heroine—just kidding!
すぐにくっついちゃえばいい
We should just get together right away,
悲劇いらない いいね?シェイクスピア
No tragedies needed, okay, Shakespeare?
やっと会えた王子様
My long-awaited prince,
まずは名前を知ることだよね
First, I need to know his name.
ヒロインらしく自然に
Naturally, like a true heroine,
バレちゃった最悪の奴らに
Caught by those awful guys who said,
「これじゃあだめ100振られる」ってどうすればいいのー!?
"'That won't do, you'll be rejected 100 times!' What should I do?!"
気持ちなら負けないなんてみんな同じこと考えてて
Everyone thinks their feelings won't lose to anyone,
そこからの勇気と押しが大事なんです
That's why courage and persistence are crucial!
聞いてる!?
Are you listening?!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ?
Pampered by a prince and everything?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね
What a dream for a plain girl like me to become a princess.
自信ちょっと付いたよ
I've gained a little confidence.
当たって砕けたらバカにして笑ってよ お願い
If I crash and burn, laugh and mock me, please!
行ってきます告白(よし)
Here I go to confess! (Alright!)
ヒロインになれ今日から
I'll become a heroine starting today!
だってだって お姫様自分
Because, because, I'm my own princess,
で決めた孤独くらいは
At least the solitude I chose
わがままにいたなきゃ
Must be treated selfishly.
人生は一度きりよ
You only live once in this life!
デスわ！
That's right!
女神 聖女 聡明 慈愛 博愛 デスわ！
Goddess, saint, wisdom, love, charity—that's right!
きっとヒロインなら綺麗で
Surely if I could be the girl of your dreams,
王子様にチヤホヤされるでしょ?
Pampered by a prince and everything?
芋女の私もお姫様になれたらなんてね
What a dream for a plain girl like me to become a princess.
動きだした運命の歯車
The gears of destiny have started turning.
今日も軽率に ステップする
Today too, I step casually,
運命の弾むような踊りです
With a dance that makes my destiny bounce.
顔を上げたその時 ほら世界が恋をする
When I lift my face, look, the world falls in love!
あたしハッピーエンドプリンセス この人生に置けるヒロイン
I'm the happy-ending princess, the heroine of this life!
突っ込んだ問題ある日々も全部全部
Even all those troublesome days head-on,
愛して見せるのよハッピーエンドプリンセス
I'll show I love them all, happy-ending princess!
自分の物語くらいは
At least my own story
気楽に楽しまなきゃ人生損損
I've got to enjoy casually, otherwise life's a loss!
先行く生き方じゃ未来は変わらない
Following ahead won't change the future,
ときめき感じて もっと自分を讃えよう
Feel the excitement and praise yourself more!
あたしハッピーエンドプリンセス 自分自身の物語くらいは
I'm the happy-ending princess, at least my own story
気楽に楽しまなきゃ損損
I've got to enjoy casually, or it's a waste!
先行く生き方じゃ未来は変わらない
Following ahead won't change the future,
ときめき感じて もっと自分を讃えよう
Feel the excitement and praise yourself more!
女神 聖女 聡明 慈愛 博愛 デスわ！
Goddess, saint, wisdom, love, charity—that's right!
超テキトーに「はいはい」
Super casually saying "Yeah, yeah"
沸点10℃のバイバイ
Saying bye at a boiling point of 10°C
PDCA言ってるけど
You keep talking about PDCA,
サバナ行ったらダサイ
but you look so uncool out in the savanna.
ぼんやり世界が病んでる感じ
The world vaguely feels like it's falling ill,
あっさり滅亡だ～ダメだ♡
A swift doom—no good!♡
その前に片想いのアイルビーラブ
Before that, my unrequited I'll Be Love
言わない uh ah 言わない
I won't say it, uh ah, I won't say it.
言うと思った?
Did you think I'd say it?
言わない uh ah 言わない
I won't say it, uh ah, I won't say it.
引かれたくない!
I don't want you to be put off!
可愛い赤ちゃんハイハイ
Cute baby, crawl crawl,
数十年後に犯罪
committing a crime decades later.
スマホばかり見てたら
Staring only at my smartphone,
ダーリングが見えない
I can't see my darling.
論破で満足するゾンビ
Zombies satisfied with destroying arguments,
反省点はどっちりけい
whose faults are which?
その前に
Before that,
愛情をアイニーチュー
give me your love, I Need You!
君の心は小学生 身長何センチ? (わーい)
Your heart is an elementary schooler, how tall are you? (Yay!)
トレンドは絶対王政 一生反抗期?(わいいわーい)
Trends are absolute monarchy, eternal rebellious phase? (Yay, yay!)
メンヘラ 病み系ラーメン 家系 ライフ 何口径?
Menhera, yami-kei ramen, iekei, life, what caliber?
地球は丸かった けど形変わっちゃった (わーい)
The Earth was round, but its shape changed (Yay!)
ピッツァは丸かった けど食べたら減っちゃったんだ(わいわーい)
Pizza was round, but it shrank once eaten (Yay, yay!)
メンヘラ 病み系ラーメン 家系 ライフ 何口径?
Menhera, yami-kei ramen, iekei, life, what caliber?
地球大爆破 どっかん uh ah どっかん
Earth explosion, dokkan, uh ah, dokkan!
死ぬと思った? どっかん uh ah どっかん
Did you think we'd die? Dokkan, uh ah, dokkan!
おせち食べたい
I want to eat osechi!
ぐだぐだの配役
Sloppy casting,
氷点下の失敗
sub-zero failure.
ちょっと滑って ゆっくり浮いて 空飛んでってワイワイ
Slipping a bit, floating slowly, flying through the sky, yay yay!
成層圏で白目を向いて 悟りの境地へ行っちゃだめ
Rolling my eyes in the stratosphere, don't go to enlightenment!
あれもダメこれもダメ
That's no good, this is no good,
検索中…
searching...
パケ死んじまった
I died of data limits!
君の実家は埼玉県
Your parents' home is in Saitama Prefecture,
住所は何番地?(わーい)
what's your address? (Yay!)
2000年代通り過ぎて
Passing through the 2000s,
秘密のパスワード(わいわーい)
a secret password (Yay, yay!)
メンヘラ 病み系ラーメン 家系 ライフ 何口径?
Menhera, yami-kei ramen, iekei, life, what caliber?
宇宙はでっかいな だけど 私はちっちゃいな(わーい)
The universe is huge, but I'm tiny (Yay!)
原子はちっちゃいな だけど 私はでっかみえた
Atoms are tiny, but I looked huge
メンヘラ 病み系ラーメン 家系 ライフ 何口径?
Menhera, yami-kei ramen, iekei, life, what caliber?
地球大爆破 どっかん uh ah どっかん
Earth explosion, dokkan, uh ah, dokkan!
死ぬと思った? どっかん uh ah どっかん
Did you think we'd die? Dokkan, uh ah, dokkan!
あっさり理性がぶっ飛ぶ感じ
A swift feeling of reason blowing away,
ぼんやり不正をやってる感じ
vaguely feeling like cheating is happening.
やめろ
Stop it
グーチョキパーで何もしない
don't make anything with rock-paper-scissors.
本当はあなたが好き 分かっているかな?
Actually, I like you. Do you know that?
君の心は小学生 (わーい)
Your heart is an elementary schooler (Yay!)
トレンドは絶対王政 一生反抗期?(わいいわーい)
Trends are absolute monarchy, eternal rebellious phase? (Yay, yay!)
メンヘラ 病み系ラーメン 家系 ライフ 何口径?
Menhera, yami-kei ramen, iekei, life, what caliber?
地球は丸かった けど形変わっちゃった (わーい)
The Earth was round, but its shape changed (Yay!)
ピッツァは丸かった けど食べたら減っちゃったんだ(わいわーい)
Pizza was round, but it shrank once eaten (Yay, yay!)
バナナをバナナと砂糖と牛乳をたっぷりふくろに加えましょ
Let's add bananas, sugar, and plenty of milk into a bag!
両手でくわっとあわせる神様
God combining them wide with both hands,
もんでもんでもんでもんで もっともっと愛をちょうだい
kneading, kneading, kneading, kneading, give me more and more love!
おんなのこに専用ジュエリー
Dedicated jewelry for girls,
かぶくわ走って乗り切れー!
Kabukuwa, run and pull through!
そーれそっそっそっそっそっそっそっそっそっそ
So-re, so-sso-sso-sso-sso...
まばたき上げてけ ゆっさゆっさゆっさゆっさゆっさゆっさゆっさゆっさ
Blink and raise it, yussa yussa...
ばんばんばんばんばんばんばんばんばん タイ湾タイ湾
Bam bam bam... Taiwan Taiwan
まった騒げー! ヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイ
Get hyped again! Hey hey hey hey...
ヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイヘイ ヘイヘイヘイヘイヘーイ!
Hey hey hey...
皆のおかげでこのライブ光のステージでアイドルできるようになったよー!
Thanks to everyone, I'm able to be an idol on this stage of light!
自分に拍手 そしてみんなに拍手!
Applause for myself, and applause for everyone!
あのビートで息が詰まるマラソン
A marathon where breath catches on that beat,
虹色グラデーション
rainbow gradation.
みんなそれぞれ愛してるけど やっぱり君が好き
I love everyone in their own way, but I still love you best!
強くギラギラ強くギラギラ強くギラギラ強くギラギラ 強くってかっこいい
Strongly glittering, strongly glittering... strong and cool!
キラキラファンタスティックな夏の思い出は宝物だよ
Sparkling, fantastic summer memories are my treasure!
今きらさん
Now, Kirasan,
かぶくわ キラキラさいこうまじ かぶくわ
Kabukuwa, sparkling, supreme, seriously Kabukuwa!
かぶくわ カブクワ イェイ! かぶくわ カブクワ
Kabukuwa, Kabukuwa, Yeah! Kabukuwa, Kabukuwa!
かぶくわ クリークリーオンメーラブ かぶくわ
Kabukuwa, curly-curly on-melody love, Kabukuwa!
かぶくわ カブくわ イェイ! かぶくわ カブくわ イェイ! かぶくわ
Kabukuwa, Kabukuwa, Yeah! Kabukuwa, Kabukuwa, Yeah! Kabukuwa!
皆のありえなーい! かぶくわ
Everyone's no way! Kabukuwa!
おてまみならべりゃ とんでるが かぶくわ
Lining up love letters and flying away, Kabukuwa!
ぱんちゅ! ちょ! ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー
Pantsu! Cho! Fire fire fire...
ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー ファイヤー イェーーイ!
Fire fire... Yeahhh!
ME・KI・ME・KI Everybody Grow Up!
ME-KI-ME-KI Everybody Grow Up!
Put your hands up ほら
Put your hands up, come on!
気分上げて 始めよう この一歩から
Raise your spirits, let's start from this step!
Let’s move my body
Let's move my body
赴くまま Exciteに高まるBeat
Go with the flow, an Excite and rising Beat!
華のように 美しく咲く
Blooming as beautifully as flowers,
凛としなやかに わびさびの魂込めて
Dignified and flexible, pouring in the soul of wabi-sabi.
目指せよ なりたい自分像
Aim for the image of yourself you want to be,
鍛えて光れDiamond
train and shine, Diamond!
挑め 限界の向こう側
Challenge the other side of your limits,
心を癒してハーモニー
soothe your heart with harmony.
夢に手伸ばしてJump! 昨日の超えてJump!
Reach out your hands to dreams and Jump! Surpassing yesterday, Jump!
Let’s Try & Try 朗らかに
Let's Try & Try cheerfully,
流した汗も 流星のように 輝き放つから
the sweat we shed shines like shooting stars!
駆け出していくStory 新しいGlory
Running forth into a Story, a new Glory—
Let’s make it make it Grow Upです
Let's make it make it Grow Up!
手を取って 頑張って 誰だって
Take hands, do your best, anyone can,
笑顔な日々が咲くように
so that smiling days can bloom!
Believe in myself
前を向いて 走り続けてこの道を
Looking forward, running continuously along this path,
Let’s get over the wall
Let's get over the wall.
独りじゃない 一緒に行こう I’m with you
You're not alone, let's go together, I'm with you!
月のように 闇間を照らす キミの笑顔で 眩い明日へ繋げて
Like the moon illuminating the darkness, connect with your smile to a dazzling tomorrow!
描けよ 誇れる自分像 鍛えて切り拓き My way
Draw your proud self-image, training and carving out My way!
もっと自分を好きになる
Loving yourself even more,
小さな勇気を分け合って
sharing small courage together,
夢に手伸ばしてJump! 昨日の超えてJump!
reach out your hands to dreams and Jump! Surpassing yesterday, Jump!
Let’s Try & Try 朗らかに
Let's Try & Try cheerfully,
流した汗も 流星のように 輝き放つから
the sweat we shed shines like shooting stars!
駆け出していくStory 新しいGlory
Running forth into a Story, a new Glory—
Let’s make it make it Grow Upです
Let's make it make it Grow Up!
手を取って 頑張って 誰だって
Take hands, do your best, anyone can,
笑顔な日々が咲くように
so that smiling days can bloom!
Believe in myself
前を向いて 走り続けてこの道を
Looking forward, running continuously along this path,
Let’s get over the wall
Let's get over the wall.
独りじゃない 一緒に行こう I’m with you
You're not alone, let's go together, I'm with you!
月のように 闇間を照らす キミの笑顔で 眩い明日へ繋げて
Like the moon illuminating the darkness, connect with your smile to a dazzling tomorrow!
描けよ 誇れる自分像 鍛えて切り拓き My way
Draw your proud self-image, training and carving out My way!
もっと自分を好きになる
Loving yourself even more,
小さな勇気を分け合って
sharing small courage together,
夢に手伸ばしてJump! 昨日の超えてJump!
reach out your hands to dreams and Jump! Surpassing yesterday, Jump!
Let’s Try & Try 朗らかに
Let's Try & Try cheerfully,
流した汗も 流星のように 輝き放つから
the sweat we shed shines like shooting stars!
駆け出していくStory 新しいGlory
Running forth into a Story, a new Glory—
Let’s make it make it Grow Upです
Let's make it make it Grow Up!
手を取って 頑張って 誰だって
Take hands, do your best, anyone can,
笑顔な日々が咲くように
so that smiling days can bloom!
Believe in myself
前を向いて 走り続けてこの道を
Looking forward, running continuously along this path,
Let’s get over the wall
Let's get over the wall.
独りじゃない 一緒に行こう I’m with you
You're not alone, let's go together, I'm with you!
ME・KI・ME・KI Everybody Grow Up!
ME-KI-ME-KI Everybody Grow Up!
みんな盛り上がってるかい！
Are you guys hyped up?!
手成熟しよう！行くめごこか？ おっけー！
Let's do a Pekora-Nene check! Shall we go? Okay!
ぺここ、こぺこ、ぺこから！このライブ最後せーの！もっともっともっともっと！
Pekoko, Kopeko, Pekora! This live final set—ready, set—more and more and more and more!
はい！ホロライブ同期みんなの心の…エナジードリンク！
Yes! Hololive generation mates, everyone's heart's... energy drink!
ねねちでコラボを忘れてた！ え？何よ？
Nene-chi, we forgot the collaboration! Eh? What?
だってさ、さっきさ、ペコラたちさ、ちょっと打ち合わせしたじゃん。 ああ、そうか！
Because, you know, earlier Pekora and us had a little meeting. Ah, that's right!
みんなにさ、「大事な〜ぺこねねだ！」って言ってもらおうぜって。 そうだそうだ！ちょっと忘れた。
To have everyone say, "It's an important Pekonene!" That's right, that's right! I kind of forgot.
じゃあみんな、あの今のやり直しで、 あの、記憶忘れってことでね、ペコラたちが二人、あの、挨拶終わったらぺこらたちで、「せーの！」っていうぺこだから
Then everyone, let's redo that current part. Since you forgot, when Pekora and I finish our greeting, Pekora will say "Ready, set!"
ペコねねだーって言ってくれました？
Did you say "Pekonene"?
やり直す？やり直す？
Should we do it over? Should we do it over?
はい、カンペキカンペキ、カンペキ！
Yes, perfect, perfect, perfect!
hololive 5th fes.のウサダ・ペコラ・アラビカ・ド・アーモンド・アーモンド！
hololive 5th fes.'s Usada Pekora-Arabica-de-Almond-Almond!
そしてhololive 5th fes.みんなのココロの、エナジードリンク・桃鈴ねねです！
And I'm Momosuzu Nene, everyone's heart's energy drink at hololive 5th fes.!
せーのっ！
Ready, set!
ありがとう！いぇーい！
Thank you! Yay!
本当にすごいぺこですね！人すごいぺこ！だいぶすごいぞ！
It's really amazing, peko! So many people, peko! This is pretty amazing!
すごいおっきい響きわたってるね！
It's echoing so massively!
いや、ほあ！やってみよっけ！あんたもやってみなよ！
Man, whoa! Try it out! Why don't you try it too?
ペコペコペコペコ…なにそれなにそれペコ！
Peko-peko-peko-peko... What is that, what is that, peko?
なんこ、え、楽しいペコだね。こうやってコール＆レスポンスするの。最高！
How many... Man, doing call-and-response like this is so fun, peko. Awesome!
楽しいペコですけれども、ペコちゃんたちはさっき未来系アイドルをちょっと歌って踊らせてもらった
It's fun, peko, but Pekora-chan and the others just got to sing and dance a bit as futuristic idols—
ねえ、もらったペコですけど、みなさんペコちゃんたちアイドルになれましたペコか？
right, peko? Everyone, did Pekora-chan and the others become idols, peko?
おおー！嬉しいペコですね！
Ooh! We're so happy, peko!
え, なんと今日はね、ねね先輩！何々？なんと国とインドネシアでもライブビューイングがあります！
Oh, and today, Nene-senpai! What is it? There are live viewings in the country and Indonesia too!
ええ！まじで！？ねねちゃん見てますかー！
Eh?! Seriously?! Nene-chan, are you watching?!
韓国のみんなも！インドネシアのみんなも！
Everyone in Korea too! Everyone in Indonesia too!
是非ね、このライブの感想をハッシュタグ「#hololivefes5th_expo」
Be sure to post your impressions of this live with the hashtag "#hololivefes5th_expo"
「#day1」でSNSでたくさんアップしてくれるとペコちゃんたちうれしペコだよね！お願いします！
and "#day1" on SNS, Pekora-chan and the others would be so happy, peko! Please do!
ハート、あ、ハート欲しいな。
Heart... ah, I want a heart.
これもおねがいします！
Please do this too!
えりお、あれ？あれれれれ？
Erio, huh? Wait, huh-huh-huh?
まてこちゃん！あった！
Wait, Pekora-chan! There it is!
でもまさかこの二人だと思ったペコなんじゃない？みんな驚いたでしょ？驚いた？どうペコ？
But you didn't think it'd be these two, did you, peko? Everyone was surprised, right? Surprised? How was it, peko?
ねねちも驚いた！ちょっと待って！ペコらとうれしいなあって思いながらこの
Nenechi was surprised too! Wait a sec! Thinking how happy I was with Pekora, this...
フェス楽しい！なにそのダンス！なになになになになに！
Fest is fun! What is that dance?! What-what-what-what-what!
ねねデリカ、いやペコらおケツが！おケツがすごいペコですけど！
Nene-delica, no, Pekora, your butt! Your butt is amazing, peko!
いやでも本当に！あれする？さっきそれちょっとコナンでレスポンス先やったんだけどさ
But seriously! Shall we do it? We did that call-and-response earlier, but...
もう一回、もう一回やる？ねねさん、だってさみんなの顔見て真顔になっちゃった！
Shall we do it one more time? Nene-san, because you looked at everyone's faces and went completely deadpan!
本当だ！なんて真顔になってるの！んな暇ないよな！
True! Why are you making a deadpan face! No time for that!
そうだよな！そうだよなー！
That's right! That's right!
え、じゃあ聞いてみようかな、いい？日本から来た人ー！
Uh, then let's ask, ready? People who came from Japan!
じゃあ、海外から来た人ー！
Then, people who came from overseas!
すごいすごい！ありがとう！
Amazing, amazing! Thank you!
まだまだ盛り上がれますかー！
Can you get even more hyped?!
嬉しいですが、なんと無料パートはここは！
We're so happy, but unfortunately, the free part ends here!
是非ともね、気になった方は概要欄からチケットが買えるので、あの、見てくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
If you're curious, you can buy tickets from the description box, so if you check it out, we'd be so happy!
よろしくお願いします！お願いします！
Please check it out! Please!
せーの、キャプチャード・モーメント！あれ？あれ？
Ready, set, Capture the Moment! Huh? Huh?
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
あの涙が今の僕らをつないで
Those tears connect us now,
この心に君のカケラがあるから一人じゃないから
because a piece of you is in this heart, and I'm not alone.
いつか描いた文字の中で目を閉じた先に色づく景色が揺れた
Inside the words I drew someday, the coloring scenery swayed beyond closed eyes.
少し戸惑う風の中 重なる花びら 私たちの声
Amidst the slightly bewildered wind, overlapping petals and our voices.
一瞬 一瞬 捕らえるみたいにもっと もっと 踏み出せたら we are one
As if capturing every single moment, if we could step forward more and more... we are one.
あの涙が今の僕らをつないでこの心に君のカケラがあるから
Those tears connect us now, because a piece of you is in this heart.
強くなくてもいい今の光を僕と集め空に放つ
It's okay not to be strong; let's gather this light together and release it to the sky.
この奇跡を僕らでそっと輝かせるから力が湧くから
We'll softly make this miracle shine together because strength wells up from within.
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended!
Thank you for watching!